https://www.sakworldpaintball.com/privacy-policy-terms-of-use-1/

Ball Hauling
Paintball Hoppers (.68 Cal Standard Size)
Chronographs
Paint + More!
Change Currency
Loading... Please wait...
Ball Hauling
Paintball Hoppers (.68 Cal Standard Size)
Chronographs
Paint + More!
Ball Hauling
Paintball Hoppers (.68 Cal Standard Size)
Chronographs
Paint + More!
Agreement with Our Terms and Conditions
By using this site, you agree to accept these terms and conditions. Make sure you read these terms and conditions carefully, because if you do choose to use our Web site, you automatically agree to them. If you do not agree with our terms and conditions, please do not use our Web site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of these terms and conditions at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our Web site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.
Sakworldpaintball.com is not responsible for typographical errors. Photos are for illustrative purposes only.  Al items carry manufacturer's warranty. Limited quantities on some items may require substitution, in which case will with ask the customer if a substitution is acceptable. Prices subject to change. Check with local law enforcement regarding legality of paintball products in your area.
Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability
None of what follows affects in any way our return policy at Sakworldpaintball.com. If for any reason you are not satisfied with a purchase that you make from our site and you have not opened the product please return it (this excludes paintballs, paintball guns and HPA tanks). Instructions on how to do so will be on the customer service page. The following, though, is important information about your use of this site.
THE Sakworldpaintball.com WEB SITE CONTENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS AND WITHOUT REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE SITE, THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, Sakworldpaintball.com DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO THIS WEB SITE OR ITS CONTENTS, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
Sakworldpaintball.com WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT ACCOMPANY OR RESULT FROM YOUR USE OF OUR WEB SITE. THESE INCLUDE (BUT ARE NOT LIMITED TO) DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY ANY USE OF (OR INABILITY TO USE) THE WEB SITE OR ANY SITE TO WHICH YOU HYPERLINK FROM OUR WEB SITE, FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INACCURACY, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, OR LINE FAILURE. FURTHERMORE, WE ARE NOT LIABLE EVEN IF WE'VE BEEN NEGLIGENT OR IF OUR AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. EXCEPTION: IN CERTAIN STATES THE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW US TO LIMIT OR EXCLUDE LIABILITY FOR THESE "INCIDENTAL" OR "CONSEQUENTIAL" DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY. THIS WEB SITE MAY CONTAIN TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS OR INACCURACIES AND MAY NOT BE COMPLETE OR CURRENT. Sakworldpaintball.com THEREFORE RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CORRECT ANY ERRORS, INACCURACIES OR OMISSIONS (INCLUDING AFTER AN ORDER HAS BEEN SUBMITTED) AND TO CHANGE OR UPDATE INFORMATION AT ANY TIME WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE. PLEASE NOTE THAT SUCH ERRORS, INACCURACIES OR OMISSIONS MAY RELATE TO PRICING AND AVAILABILITY. WE APOLOGIZE FOR ANY INCONVENIENCE.
Additional Points about the Terms and Conditions of this User Agreement
These terms and conditions and the agreement they create, shall be governed by and interpreted according to the laws of the State of Massachusetts (without applying the State's conflict-of-law principles). Sakworldpaintball.com reserves the right to bring any civil action in Massachusetts , arising from your violation of the terms and conditions of this Agreement. If any provision of this agreement is unlawful, void or unenforceable, it will not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. Sakworldpaintball.com may modify these terms and conditions, and the agreement they create, at any time, simply by updating this posting and without notice to you. This is the entire agreement regarding all the matters that have been discussed in the preceding paragraphs.
Use of Information that You Provide
At Sakworldpaintball.com we collect personal information only for the purposes of fulfilling orders, providing a high level of customer service, gaining knowledge internally regarding what our customers want and mailing circulars and special offers from Sakworldpaintball.com. We do not give or sell Personal Information to any other party, except to those of our employees who we rely on to handle this information on our behalf in accordance with the above purposes.
Security of the Information You Provide
Among our top priorities is keeping your Personal Information secure. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which provides the highest level of security currently available for secure transactions, to encrypt all of your Personal Information before it is transmitted to us. Encrypted information cannot be read or recorded as it travels over the Internet. You can tell you are sending information securely by the unbroken key icon or closed lock icon on that should appear at the bottom of your internet browser's window (depending on what browser you use). These icons will appear when you are placing an order on our Web site. In addition, you will see our site address change slightly, from http: to https: indicating a secure server connection is being used.
Additionally, access to your Personal Information is provided only to our employees who have a need to know such information for the purpose of fulfilling your order and offering our high level of customer service. The computers that store your Personal Information employs the latest in firewall and security technology.
If you prefer not to disclose your credit card information online, you can always place your order by calling 978-686-2840
Your Acceptance of these Terms
By using our Web site, you agree to accept the Sakworldpaintball.com privacy policy. Make sure you read this policy carefully, because if you do choose to use our Web site, you automatically agree to this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Web site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our Web site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
SIGN UP FOR OUR LATEST NEWS &AMP SPECIAL OFFERS
Email
STAY CONNECTED:
877-SAKWORLD (725-9675)
Information:
Your Account:
